100/120, Soi 8, Nakkeelalamtong Village., Krungthepkreetha Road, Sapansoong District ◆ Bangkok, 10250 ◆ 086-358-2358, 02-368-2734 ◆ Mastercreativity@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE: To pursue a challenging leadership position applying creative problem solving and

lean management skills with a growing company to achieve optimum utilization of

its resource and maximum profits.

SUMMARY: Over 12 years of increasing responsibilities in online, business and partnership

development, sales and marketing regarding IT, retail, food & beverage, financial service industries, and e-Business. Additional experience in corporate marketing, credit card promotion, social commerce, mobile commerce, budget management, and demonstrated success in acquiring, converting, retaining and managing channel

partners.

Result and solutions oriented, insatiable curiosity for all online and digital things, well-rounded eCommerce professional with experience in online banking and digital marketing, successfully and consistently delivering the responsibilities of revenue generation, profitability, market share, and customer satisfaction.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Online Biz Development Manager

Krungthai Card PCL (H.O.), Thailand

Jun 2015 to Nov 2015

- Created business plan for online merchant acquiring team
- Educated sales to input online payment gateway knowledge for cross-selling (EDC, mPos, PGW)
- Involved in new payment platform and tools project including O2O (Online to Offline) Alipay
- Conducted analysis and forecast for eCommerce & mCommerce transformation
- Innovated various e-Business solutions with expertise in analyzing business requirements
- Partnered with Payment Service Provider (PSP) to create new business model for merchants
- Strategically forecasted, planned, and implemented online marketing campaigns
- Created digital support plan and training modules to enhance the merchant leaded from KTB
- Aided digital marketing team to implement new technology and new payment method for online payment gateway such as Passbook (Apple), iBeacon, Paypal, MasterPass, QR code payment
- Developed monthly report, analyzed the key issues, and updated to EVP and CEO

Business Development Manager

True Digital Content and Media Co., Ltd., Thailand

Sep 2013 to May 2015

- Strategically planned and implemented e-Commerce & m-Commerce marketing campaigns mainly
 focused on www.iTrueMart.com (TDCM are also operating Weloveshopping.com, the biggest online
 marketplace in Southeast Asia and Store.truecorp.co.th as one-spot online retail for True Shop)
- Partnered with all banks for various medias and for card privilege, increase over 60% of traffic (UIP) and over 30% of conversion rate
- Allocated credit card promotions increased over 50% of spending in 3 months (Oct-Dec 2014)
- Leaded on iTrueMart mobile app project, concluded final design and process, established best practice for UI&UX, accurately assessed problem and quickly generated a resolution
- Created online shopping campaign via LINE Official Account TrueMove H & True You
- Strategically built e-Business plans and project initiatives
- Conducted analysis and forecast for e-Commerce & m-Commerce transformation
- Innovated various e-Business solutions with expertise in analyzing business requirements
- Participated in management e-Business roadmap
- Reported e/m-Commerce & digital marketing trends, tools, and techniques, prepared the monthly report analysis, and provided commentary on the overhead budget to Deputy Director/President

Marketing (e-Commerce) Executive

Bangkok Bank PCL. (H.O.), Thailand

Aug 2011 to Aug 2013

- Increased over 20% of total volume from over 500 merchants
- Created worldwide digital support plan and training modules for new-to-market merchants; reduce next generation support cost by 25%
- Customized training programs to align with different natures of online businesses including how to
 professionally sale products/services online including web design, shipping, refund policies, promo
 code, digital marketing, and provided solutions to both new and existing merchants, resulting in
 immediate revenue improvement of up to 100%
- Instructed Branch Managers all over 1,000 Branches in Thailand to ensure that all educational initiatives of online solutions were completely understand and be able to share and provide the process in details
- Assisted IT manager to implement new technology and function for online payment gateway such as installment, multi-based currencies, mPos, IPSP (local/inter)
- Planned an e-Commerce project focusing on acquiring business
- Participated in management action-plan & marketing meeting

Marketing Manager

Thai Cottage INC., United State

Aug 2008 to May 2011

- Strategically forecasted, planned, and implemented marketing campaigns
- Planned and controlled policy and team to work related to overall concept of public relation and fullservice restaurant's marketing
- Discovered and created massive of new potential customers from being an online marketing team leader, and achieved highest record of Groupon sold (over 4,000 coupons were purchased by online advertising within 3 hours) with Groupon.com
- Created the monthly report analysis and provided commentary on the overhead budget
- Achieved company objectives in sales, cost saving with best quality, appearance of facility and customers' satisfaction
- Participated in management monthly meeting and marking decision with Founders

Marketing Analyst

Canon Marketing (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

Oct 2005 to May 2006

- Strategically forecasted, planned, and implemented marketing campaigns
- Controlled the budgets for marketing event and all advertising
- Consistently arranged product placement from regional branch (Singapore)
- Prepared all up-country events and following up commercial issues of dealers
- Organized launch celebrations and generated dealers interest in new products
- Taught over 70 Sales in Office Solution Department focusing on new products features and benefits including large format printer, multi-function copier, and facsimile
- Utilized sales feedbacks to create better comprehensive product-training program
- Developed and updated user manuals for new and existing products

Sales Representative

Asia Books Co., Ltd., Thailand

Sep 2004 to Sep 2005

- Consistently achieved a monthly sales target
- Maintained and improved superior customer relationships
- Achieved top 10 sales performers in the company comprised of over 10 stores

INTERNSHIP

Performance Indicator (TQM) Officer

Bumrungrad International Hospital, Thailand

Jun 2004 to Aug 2004

Marketing Trainee

Property Perfect Public Co., Ltd., Thailand

Aug 2003 to May 2004

General Clerks

Aksorn Charoen Tat Act. Co., Ltd., Thailand

April 2003 to Jul 2003

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration concentration in Global Management

GPA: 3.83

University of Houston -Victoria, Houston, TX

Aug 2008 to May 2010

Activities and Societies: - Member of the Global Management Association National Honor Society

- Presidential member of the National Society of Leadership and Success

Coursework Highlights: "Global Economics, Financial Reporting & Analysis, Int'l Finance,

Int'l Marketing, Int'l Operation Management, Int'l Business Strategy"

Bachelor of Administration concentration in Marketing

GPA: 3.24

Chandrakasem Rajabhat University-Bangkok, Thailand

Aug 2000 to May 2004

Activities and Societies: - Member of Marketing Association

- Participated in various marketing training programs for marketing students

- Foundation member of the Social Work Students

- Top 10 Marketing students graduated in 2004

TRAINING

Mobile First, Win First, Shoppenning

August 26, 2015

- Mobile case study & trend in 2016, O2O and Omni channel

Payment Service Provider (PSP), VISA Thailand

February 21, 2013

- New card acceptance regulations, surcharge

Social Media & Mobile Payment, National Technological University

September 13, 2012

- New trend & security for mobile user, smartphone behavior, and mPOS

PCI-DSS, VISA Thailand

May 16, 2012

- PCI-DSS, Online Payment Security, Fraud and dispute cases

Digital Marketing, The Tourism Authority of Thailand (TAT)

February 17, 2012

- New Online Market for travel and hotel businesses

Online Marketing in 2012, Online/digital Marketing

January 17, 2012

- Google Analytics/Ads, SEO, SEM, and E- commerce Trend

REPRESENTATIVE SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

- Have a good understanding of e-Business, e-Commerce, m-Commerce, s-Commerce, online/digital content & marketing, social media including Line, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Blogger and YouTube
- Have experience of LINE mobile business model and other mobile commerce campaigns
- Knowledge of basic and advance used for mobile banking application including iBanking (BBL), K-Moblie Plus (KBANK), SCB Easy & Up2Me (SCB), Click & Tap (KTC), Money Service (TESCO)
- Excellent computer skills (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook, LotusNote, Cardlink, Lightroom)
- Excellent English skills with speaking, writing and listening
- Excellent presentation and motivation skills
- Possess a excellent sales & marketing background
- Possess the successful business negotiation skills
- Possess the ability to work well with others

References upon request ◆ Amplified resume online at www.linkedin.com/in/sirot2010

- ♦ Current Salary: 110,000 THB (\$ 100,000 + 🗈 5,000 + 🕿 3,000 + 🗷 2,000)
 - ♦ Bonus 4-6 mo. (fixed 1 mo.) & PF 5.5%

